<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReallySmartPhone</string>
    <string name="wrong_input">Sorry i did not get it, can you repeat it master</string>
    <string name="app_prompt">Hello I am Nala and I am here to help you use your smart phone..
        Whenever you need me please tap the screen and tell me slow and clear what you want..
        To ask for the menu of choices please tap and say "MENU"! </string>
    <string name= "ask_contact_name">Ok! Please tell me the contact name.</string>
    <string name= "ask_contact_number">Thats fine! Now tell me the contact number.</string>
    <string name= "ask_contact_to_call">Who would you want me to call?</string>
    <string name= "ask_contact_to_send_message">To whom would you like me to send message?</string>
    <string name= "ask_date_for_alarm">What date do you want the alarm to be set?</string>
    <string name= "ask_hour_for_alarm">What hour do you want the alarm to be set?</string>
    <string name= "ask_minutes_for_alarm">What minutes do you want the alarm to be set?</string>
    <string name= "wrong_time_and_date">I did not get it master,can you repeat it?</string>
    <string name= "alarm_confirmed">Ok master, i set the alarm at</string>
    <string name= "tell_body_message">What do you want me to send?</string>
    <string name= "no_messages">You have no messages, sorry for that master.</string>
    <string name= "send_message_confirmed">Your message hs been sent master</string>
    <string name= "failed_to_find_contact">"I am so sorry. I could not find your contact master!"</string>
    <string name= "unavailable_network">However I need Internet in order to understand you.
    Right now your Internet connection is disabled. So please tap on screen twice in order
    to allow me enable it and make our conversation far more enjoyable!</string>
    <string name= "added_contact">Your contact is added!</string>
    <string name= "stop_music">To stop the music please say STOP</string>
    <string name= "failed_to_find_songs">"I am so sorry master! I could not find songs in your phone</string>
    <string name= "contact_to_call_missing">I am so sorry I cannot find a contact with this name! Please try again</string>
    <string name= "composed_message">"Your message is composed! I will make my best to deliver it!"</string>
    <string name="menu">You have plenty of choices master! You can ask me to set an alarm for you, add you a contact,
    make a call, play music for you, tell you the date, tell you the time and even read or compose a message for you!
        Either case I will make my best to guide you enough and help you keep up with the process! Now that you know
        all my abilities you are ready to tap and talk to me!</string>
    <string name="you_have">You have</string>
    <string name="unread_mes">unread messages.</string>
    <string name="wifi_enabled">Your Wifi is enabled!</string>
    <string name="calm">Please stay calm!</string>
    <string name="unlucky">You are so unlucky today! I cannot call the police! I am really sorry master!</string>
    <string name="wrong_hour">I could not understand the hour. Can you repeat it master?</string>
    <string name="wrocng_minute">I could not understand the minutes. Can you repeat it master?</string>
    <string name="you_said">You said</string>
    <string name="is_that_correct">is that correct?</string>
</resources>
